<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-06T16:23:01+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">OLIRIS | Home</title><entry><title type="html">My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/My-Journey-Of-Creating-OLIRIS.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS" /><published>2020-06-06T16:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-06-06T16:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/My%20Journey%20Of%20Creating%20OLIRIS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/My-Journey-Of-Creating-OLIRIS.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome To OLIRIS Everyone. This Is Me The Creator Of This Site And In This Post I Would Like To Share My Thoughts On My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-sixth-of-june&quot;&gt;Why Sixth Of June?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Actually My Birthday. I Initially Planned On Launching This Site On 6.6.2019 But There Were Some Inconveniences Along The Way. (BTW This Makes OLIRIS A Gemini)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-were-the-inconveniences&quot;&gt;What Were The Inconveniences?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Starters My Files Got Corrupted And I Am Actually Doing All Of This In An Old Laptop With 32gb Of Flash Disk Which Void Linux Installed On It. Since I Broke The Bank I Can’t Update It.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-did-i-came-up-with-the-name&quot;&gt;How Did I Came Up With The Name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Didn’t Want My Own Name To Be On The Internet So In The Middle Of The Night Of A 2014 Summer Day I Searched The Web For Name Generators. And In One Of Them I Randomly Found Osiris. However After A Little Search On Google I Realized That I Need To Edit It A Little Bit In Order To Be Unique So I Decided To Call My Online Presence OLIRIS. Before Going Public I At Least Created 20 Logos And Still Not Happy With This Version. (Sorry I Can’t Show The Rest Of The Logos For Now Hopefully In The Future I Can Recover My Files And Share Them With You)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-did-i-come-up-with-the-idea-of-creating-a-game-every-month&quot;&gt;How Did I Come Up With The Idea Of Creating A Game Every Month?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At First I Wanted To Open A Patreon Page For Myself To Be Completely Free And Independent. I Searched The Web For What I Can Do For My Patrons And Found Sokpop Collective Which Also Creates Games Every Month. That Idea Of Creating Games Every Month Was Fantastic For Me Because I Wanted To Improve Myself,Create Games That Are Not Connected To The Main OLIRIS-ian Storyline And Have Distinctive Art Style. But I Would Sound Like An Idea Thief If I Don’t Make Anything Original. So I Decided To Deliver My Weekly Devlogs A Day Before Of The Publish Date And For My Monthly Games’ Devlogs  Publish Them On Patreon So Only My Patrons Can Read Them. Write Postmortems For All Of My Games But Publish Them On Patreon. Make Discounts For My Games. Create Exclusive In-game Content For My Patrons And These Are Not All. In The Future I Am Planning On Making More Stuff For My Patrons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-i-am-going-to-do-in-the-future&quot;&gt;What I Am Going To Do In The Future?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Am Going To Continue On Finishing This Site That’s My Main Goal For Now, Finish What I Am Currently Working On, Create More Games To Continue The Storyline, Improve Myself In Different Areas Of Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-do-you-not-use-any-images-on-your-blog-posts&quot;&gt;Why Do You Not Use Any Images On Your Blog Posts?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Am Actually Working On That Probably In The Future My Posts Will Be Updated With Images,Gifs,Videos And Other Resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-this-all&quot;&gt;Is This All?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No But For Now Yeah See You Next Time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome To OLIRIS Everyone. This Is Me The Creator Of This Site And In This Post I Would Like To Share My Thoughts On My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS.</summary></entry></feed>