<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-27T13:43:24+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">OLIRIS | Home</title><entry><title type="html">Weekly Devlog #4</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/27/Weekly-Devlog-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Devlog #4" /><published>2020-07-27T06:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-07-27T06:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/07/27/Weekly%20Devlog#4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/27/Weekly-Devlog-4.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Guys And Welcome Back To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Week And Show You The Current State Of My Games. But Before We Begin Let Me Tell You Beginning Of This Week Was AMAZING But At The End It Got Dark. Classic 2020 Week It’s Nothing Special. Anyways Let’s Begin The Devlog&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BTW I’m Sorry I Wasn’t Able To Edit The Videos So They Are Out Of Size And Unoptimesed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-war&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Week I Implemented Two Left Clicking On A Unit To Select Across  The Screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/SelectAll.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I Fixed Another Bug On The Deployment Depertment. It Should Use Less Memory Now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Finished Inventory. You Can Rearange The Deck, Duplicate Them, Delete And Add New Decks.
There Is Also Prefab Decks That Are Preconfigured And Ready To Add To Your Current Deck Collection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/InventoryAllDone.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Added A Label That Tells You Why You Were’nt Able To Use An Ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Label.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Also Changed The Requirements System Of The Abilities. It Should Function Properly Now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello Guys And Welcome Back To OLIRIS . Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Week And Show You The Current State Of My Games. But Before We Begin Let Me Tell You Beginning Of This Week Was AMAZING But At The End It Got Dark. Classic 2020 Week It’s Nothing Special. Anyways Let’s Begin The Devlog</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekly Devlog #3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/20/Weekly-Devlog-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Devlog #3" /><published>2020-07-20T06:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-07-20T06:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/07/20/Weekly%20Devlog#3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/20/Weekly-Devlog-3.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome Back To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Week And Show You The Current State Of My Games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-have-i-been-doing&quot;&gt;What Have I Been Doing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If You Have Noticed There Wasn’t A Devlog Last Week, The Reason Was I Joined The GMTK Game Jam. It Was 2 Days Long Jam And The Theme Was Out Of Control. Here Is Submisson To The Jam &lt;a href=&quot;Stay Alive But Random&quot;&gt;https://oliris.itch.io/stay-alive-but-random&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-war&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Was Only Able To Fix A Bug That Involved With Miscelenious Buildings(Power Plants, Civilian Buildings, Etc.) Which When Selected They Were Able To Open The Panel. And Since They Don’t Have Anyhting To Deploy The Panel Was Empty. Now This Is All Fixed And Maybe In The Future I Will Update The Panel To Show More Information About The Building That’s Currently Selected (Which I Am Planning A New UI For The Game)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Panel.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Finally Started Implementing The Invontory. Currently It Only Shows The All Avalible Abilities And Decks Of The Player. And For Now You Can Only Create Empty Decks.
The Way You Open The Inventory Is By Holding Down “~” Key.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Inventory.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Added Shooting In The Game But It’s In Very Rough State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Also Added The First Enemy But Since It’s The First Implemention It’s Very Rough. It Only Detects The Player, Follows And Shoot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Finally I Added An Attack Indicator But It Doesn’t Correctly Show Where The Player Get Hit. Hopefully Next Week I Will Fix It.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Enemy.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome Back To OLIRIS . Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Week And Show You The Current State Of My Games.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekly Devlog #2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/06/Weekly-Devlog-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Devlog #2" /><published>2020-07-06T09:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-07-06T09:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/07/06/Weekly%20Devlog#2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/06/Weekly-Devlog-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome Back To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Last Week And Show You The Current Process Of My Games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Before We Begin I Would Like To Title This Week As One Of My Most Productive Weeks Of Last Month(June).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-war&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Fixed A Bug With Deployment Buttons. Before If You Were Holding An Building And Pressed One Of The Buttons The Building Would’ve Left In The Scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/DeployBtnFix.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Added An Visual Way Of Telling Which Gmae Mode You Are Currently In (I’m Talking About Selling And Repair) It’s Just An Rect That Changes It’s Border Colors To Yellow Or Blue But It’s Still Something. Also I Fixed A Bug Involved In Cycling Between The Game Modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/GamemodeUI.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Finally Added Requirements System To The Abilities. In The Current State I Don’t It’s Well Optimized Hopefully I Will Make It More Optimized In The Upcoming Weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Requirements.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Fixed Dashing. Before Dashing Was Limited On The Global X Axis. Now You Should Dash Through Where You Are Facing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/DashingFix.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Added An Ability Of Spawning A Platform Underneath You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/PlatformAbility.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also I Fixed A Bug In Abilities’ Buttons. Before If You Switched To Another Weapon, The Abilities Weren’t Able To Remember Their Cooldown. Now They Should Remember How Many Time Left And Show It Accordingly On Their Buttons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/CooldownFix.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Also Added The Foundation Of Shooting And Secondary Ability Of The Weapons (I Can’t Demonstrate Them Now But Keep Your Eyes On The Next Week)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;next-week&quot;&gt;Next Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m Planning On 3D Assets (Finally!) Because There Is Nothing Much Left On Coding For Now Except For A Proper Inventory System For Tales Of Heroes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome Back To OLIRIS . Today I Am Here To Show You What I Was Up To This Last Week And Show You The Current Process Of My Games.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekly Devlog #1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/29/Weekly-Devlog-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Devlog #1" /><published>2020-06-29T12:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-06-29T12:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/29/Weekly%20Devlog#1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/29/Weekly-Devlog-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome Back To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Today I Am Going To Talk About What I’ve Been Doing For Last Two Weeks And Show You The Current State Of The Games That I’m Working On.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Of All I Have To Apologize All Of You For Not Working Hard These Two Weeks. I Kinda Struggled With My Own Life And Work Balance. Hopefully This Week I Can Work Like I Intended&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-war&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Added Repair System For Buildings. I Used Timer Node Of Godot And Attached A Script That Increases Building’s Health According To An Public Editable Float Variable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/RepairShowcase.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Tried Adding Fog Of War Using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VY2I7XdvsMY&quot;&gt;His Idea&lt;/a&gt;. But I Shader Didn’t Worked For Me So I Abandoned That Idea And Started Looking For Other Alternatives For This Problem. I Found Out Godot’s CSG Shape. I Added CSGCombiner Node To The Scene With A Cube Primitive And Added Cylinder Primitive To The Unit Nodes. But Even Though Setting Boolean Operation On Combiner It Didn’t Worked How I Wanted It To. Hopefully This Week I Will Find Something For This Issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixed Camera Rotation On Third Person View.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/CameraRotationFixTOH.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And That’s Unfortunately It. Again I’m Terribly Sorry About These Two Weeks. See You Next Time Hopefully With More Updates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome Back To OLIRIS . Today I Am Going To Talk About What I’ve Been Doing For Last Two Weeks And Show You The Current State Of The Games That I’m Working On.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekly Devlog #0</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Weekly-Devlog-0.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Devlog #0" /><published>2020-06-15T12:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-06-15T12:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Weekly%20Devlog#0</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Weekly-Devlog-0.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome Back To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Today I Am Going To Talk About What I’ve Been Doing For The Last Couple Of Weeks And Show The Games’ Current Development State. So Let’s Begin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-war&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Up I Almost Finished Placement System Of The Game. I Set Up A Grid System With Godot’s In Engine 3D Tiles GridMap. Then I Added Boundary System That Changes Building’s Material Depending On If It’s Placeable Or Not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Placement.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Re Factored The Selection System To Be More Efficient And Easy To Read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Selection.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With The Re Factoring Process I Also Fixed A Bug In The UI. The Bug Was If You Clicked Somewhere Empty On The Panels It Would’ve De Select Everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Also Added Health System With Health Bars On Top Of Units And Buildings. It Still Lacks Design Tho.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/HealthSystem.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I Started This Project 2 Weeks Ago So The Game Is In A Very Rough State. Please Keep That In Mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching Between First Person To Third Person (Please Don’t Mind How The Cross-air Looks.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Camswitch.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Added Ability System Which Makes The Player Do Some Stuff Like Double Jumping, Sliding Left Or Right, Dashing Etc. You Can Active Them With Keyboard Or Pressing The Abilities Button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/Abilities.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Added Health System With A Health Bar. It Also Lacks Design Too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;video SRC=&quot;/SRC/Video/Posts/HealthHereos.mp4&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Actually That Was All The Things That I Did For Tales Of Heroes This Week. Hopefully Next Week Will Be More Productive Than This Week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-i-have-to-do-this-week&quot;&gt;What I Have To Do This Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tales-of-war-1&quot;&gt;Tales Of War&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fog Of War&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repairing System&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3D Assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tales-of-heroes-1&quot;&gt;Tales Of Heroes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add Rotation To Third Person Mode&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Requirement System For Abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Writing. That’s The Only Part Of The Game That Needs To Be Done ASAP. Because Game Lacks The Story I Don’t Know What To Do&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UI (Especially An Cross-air Texture)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3D Assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other-stuff&quot;&gt;Other Stuff&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I Also Have To Some Pages About The Games.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;And This Month’s Game For Patreon.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And That Was All. Thank You For Reading I Hope To See You Next Time With More Updates On The Games.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome Back To OLIRIS . Today I Am Going To Talk About What I’ve Been Doing For The Last Couple Of Weeks And Show The Games’ Current Development State. So Let’s Begin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/MyJourneyOfCreatingOLIRIS.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS" /><published>2020-06-06T16:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-06-06T16:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/MyJourneyOfCreatingOLIRIS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/06/MyJourneyOfCreatingOLIRIS.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome To &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt; Everyone. This Is Me The Creator Of This Site And In This Post I Would Like To Share My Thoughts On My Journey Of Creating &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-sixth-of-june&quot;&gt;Why Sixth Of June?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Actually My Birthday. I Initially Planned On Launching This Site On 6.6.2019 But There Were Some Inconveniences Along The Way. (BTW This Makes &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt; A Gemini)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-were-the-inconveniences&quot;&gt;What Were The Inconveniences?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Starters My Files Got Corrupted And I Am Actually Doing All Of This In An Old Laptop With 32gb Of Flash Disk Which Void Linux Installed On It. Since I Broke The Bank I Can’t Update It.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-did-i-came-up-with-the-name&quot;&gt;How Did I Came Up With The Name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Didn’t Want My Own Name To Be On The Internet So In The Middle Of The Night Of A 2014 Summer Day I Searched The Web For Name Generators. And In One Of Them I Randomly Found Osiris. However After A Little Search On Google I Realized That I Need To Edit It A Little Bit In Order To Be Unique So I Decided To Call My Online Presence &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;. Before Going Public I At Least Created 20 Logos And Still Not Happy With This Version. (Sorry I Can’t Show The Rest Of The Logos For Now Hopefully In The Future I Can Recover My Files And Share Them With You)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-did-i-come-up-with-the-idea-of-creating-a-game-every-month&quot;&gt;How Did I Come Up With The Idea Of Creating A Game Every Month?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At First I Wanted To Open A Patreon Page For Myself To Be Completely Free And Independent. I Searched The Web For What I Can Do For My Patrons And Found Sokpop Collective Which Also Creates Games Every Month. That Idea Of Creating Games Every Month Was Fantastic For Me Because I Wanted To Improve Myself,Create Games That Are Not Connected To The Main &lt;span class=&quot;Logo&quot;&gt;OLIRIS &lt;/span&gt;-ian Storyline And Have Distinctive Art Style. But I Would Sound Like An Idea Thief If I Don’t Make Anything Original. So I Decided To Deliver My Weekly Devlogs A Day Before Of The Publish Date And For My Monthly Games’ Devlogs  Publish Them On Patreon So Only My Patrons Can Read Them. Write Postmortems For All Of My Games But Publish Them On Patreon. Make Discounts For My Games. Create Exclusive In-game Content For My Patrons And These Are Not All. In The Future I Am Planning On Making More Stuff For My Patrons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-i-am-going-to-do-in-the-future&quot;&gt;What I Am Going To Do In The Future?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Am Going To Continue On Finishing This Site That’s My Main Goal For Now, Finish What I Am Currently Working On, Create More Games To Continue The Storyline, Improve Myself In Different Areas Of Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-do-you-not-use-any-images-on-your-blog-posts&quot;&gt;Why Do You Not Use Any Images On Your Blog Posts?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Am Actually Working On That Probably In The Future My Posts Will Be Updated With Images,Gifs,Videos And Other Resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-this-all&quot;&gt;Is This All?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No But For Now Yeah See You Next Time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome To OLIRIS Everyone. This Is Me The Creator Of This Site And In This Post I Would Like To Share My Thoughts On My Journey Of Creating OLIRIS .</summary></entry></feed>